翻譯: Amber Heisenberg 皮皮 月餅
嘿 Danny 你的三明治
Hey, Danny, your sandwich
校對: 三好
在冰箱里放了有一個月了吧
has been in the fridge for, like, a month.
- 我帶回去當晚飯了  - 蹲下 別出聲
- I'm taking it home for dinner. - Down, get down. Shh.
等等 什么 什么情況
Wait, what? Wait, what's happening?
- 我應該帶上我的泰瑟槍嗎  - 這里
- Should I get my taser? - Osama.
后期: 大塊頭要冷靜
- 謝謝你啊 Mindy 我被干掉了  - 好吧 我能不能說句話
- Great, Mindy, you got me killed. - Okay, can I just say...
壓制: BB
太不公平了 你們就可以做這些蠢事
It is so unfair that it's cool for you
而我 不過是希望所有醫生
to do all this dumb stuff, but I just wanted all the doctors
一起給Meredith Vieira錄首生日歌
to sing one birthday video for Meredith Vieira,
Meredith Vieira 美國著名記者 電視名人和游戲秀節目主持
突然就變成"這是工作的地方"了
and suddenly "It's a workplace."
現在是下班時間 規矩變了
It's after hours. There's different rules.
啊哈
Aah!
- Peter在哪 Peter在哪  - 在這呢
- Where's Peter? Where's Peter? - I'm right here.
- 放下槍 否則我就斃了她  - 啊 啊
- Put the gun down, or she gets it. - Aah! Aah!
- 你不會這么做的  - 我會殺了這個老女人
- You're not gonna do it. - I will kill this old lady.
- 你說什么  - 她馬上就55歲了
- Excuse me? - She's pushing 55,
這時候死去是很不幸的
and that's a terrible day to die.
- 不 不是 我很年輕的  - 放下槍
- No, that's not... I'm not. I'm young. - Drop the gun.
- 我不知道他是  - 嘿
- I don't know what he's... - Hey.
你亂動什么 想跑哪去啊 你現在就是砧板上的肉好嗎
Where are you jumping off to, you little piece of bacon?
我還沒打算放過你呢
I ain't ready to take you out of the pan.
- 聞起來不錯  - 好吧
- Ah, smells nice. - All right...
帶著這么迷人的氣味死去 多么可惜啊
Be sad if she died smellin' so purty, wouldn't it?
- 他知道這只是個游戲吧  - 都給我閉嘴
- He knows this is a game, right? - Everybody, shut up.
我莊嚴宣誓 在這面神圣的 你說
I pledge allegiance to the flag... say it...
美利堅奧巴馬合眾國旗下
Of the United States of Obama's America.
這是演哪出啊
What character is this?
我需要思考 所有人安靜
I need to think. Everybody be quiet.
放下槍
Put the gun down.
讓他去死吧 我就可以回家去看電視了
Let him kill himself, so I can go home and watch TV.
好吧 好吧 好吧
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
- 不太公平啊  - 我說 這真是個
- That seems unfair. - Okay, well, this was a dumb...
超級傻又浪費時間的事 Peter
Hugely dumb waste of time, Peter.
嗷 我的胸
Ow! My boob!
痛 你射中我的胸了
Ow! You shot both my boobs.
射中了大的 小的也要平等對待啊
Well, once I shot the big one, I had to get the small one too.
你再說一遍 兩邊一樣大的好嗎
How dare you? They're both huge.
你為什么這么抓狂 這不過是<翅膀與疼痛>
I don't know why you're freaking out. It's wings and stings.
- 翅膀在那兒  - 疼痛在這兒
- Wings. - And stings!
- 嗷  - 哇哦
- Ow! - Whoa!
我恨你們 我恨這里
I hate this. I hate working here!
- 你一直藏在那嗎  - 整整一個小時呢
- You were hiding there the whole time? - For an hour.
挑的好 好地方
That was a good spot, that was a good spot.
明迪煩事多    第二季 第六集
電波誠譯
我把大家召集過來 是因為我有一個好主意
Well, I gathered you all here because I have an idea
可以讓我們的工作地點煥然一新
that I believe will revolutionize this workplace.
我們不會出資買酸奶機的
We're not getting a fro-yo machine.
你永遠都不會更換過濾器
You'll never change the filter.
- 結果我們最后全得了肺炎  - 不是那件事 Danny
- We'll all get legionnaires' disease. - It's not that, Danny.
我們有這么美的戶外空間 卻一直沒有加以利用
We have this beautiful outdoor space that we don't use at all,
除了Danny會偷偷跑來抽煙
except Danny comes out here to smoke, in secret.
- 好吧  - 所以我向大家隆重介紹
- Okay... - So I would like to give you...
Mindy Lahiri出品 舒爾曼及合伙人診所的
Mindy Lahiri presents: The Shulman and Associates
露臺花園 寧靜之地
gazebo garden and serenity space.
- 哇 好美啊  - 謝謝
- Ah, it's beautiful. - Thank you.
為什么要加一只大蜘蛛在那
I don't get why we want a giant spider.
滾開 該死的蟲子
Get of here, you son of a bitch.
- 酷  - 一個沒人喜歡的主意
- Cool... - An idea that no one likes.
你知道我們應該怎么做嗎 擺一個燒烤架
You know what we should do? Put a grill out here.
這樣 當病人在等檢查結果的時候
That way, we could cook
我們就可以在這里
up some steaks and some ribs for the patients
給他們烤點牛排 肋骨什么的
while they wait for their paps.
我更喜歡這個主意 真的 對不起
I like his idea better, I do. I'm so sorry.
不不不 你們誤會了
Oh, no, no, we're not brainstorming.
我不是來征求意見的 這事已經定下來了
I'm not taking suggestions. This already went down, sorry.
我真的更喜歡Peter的想法
I really like Peter's idea.
我的意思是 你想想啊
I mean, you know, why do
我們為什么會需要一個露臺呢 那完全沒用啊
we we need a gazebo, right? It's useless.
Danny 第一 你可以帶你的真愛來這里
Danny, for one, you can come here and wait out a rainstorm
一起看大雨傾盆而下
with your one true love or, like,
或者在月光下跳舞
go dancing in the moonlight,
你也可以在這里過煙癮
or you can smoke, you nicotine addict.
噢 我又有一個點子
Oh, you know what else we should do?
用水泥瀝青把花壇蓋掉
We should cover this flower bed with cement
在上面建一個籃球架
and asphalt and put up a basketball hoop.
噢 太棒了 兄弟你真天才
Ohh! Okay, right there. That's genius, right there.
也不會有人得肺病什么的了
And nobody gets legionnaires' disease.
我們會建一個露臺 管你們怎么想
We're getting a gazebo, damn it.
也許在春天加個朔節花柱 可以跳舞
And maybe a maypole in the spring for dancing.
五朔節 古老的北半球春季節日
朔節花柱是一種節日裝飾 有繞花柱起舞的節日習俗
Morgan 把這堆垃圾清了 以便我憤然而去
Morgan, please clear this trash, so I can storm out.
垃圾快滾
Get out of the way!
你根本沒在幫忙 你沒在幫忙
You're doing nothing, you're doing nothing.
不 這個
No, no, it...
啊
Aah!
你能感覺出什么區別嗎
Can you tell the difference?
- 讓我看看能不能  - 啊 啊 輕點輕點
- Let me see if I can take... - Aah, aah! Tap out, tap out!
喔 痛死了
Oh, oh, ooh.
你們在搞什么啊
What the hell, you guys?
不得不說 兄弟
I gotta say, dude, that was a
你比我想象得持久多了
lot longer than I thought you were gonna last.
太棒了
That was amazing.
- 那是什么  - 終極決斗
- What was that? - Ultimate fighting.
就像是拳擊加摔跤加格斗
It's like boxing, plus wrestling, plus strangling.
對我的麥片酥說吧
Well, tell it to my granola bar,
掉在地上 全都是灰
which fell on the ground and is now covered in dirt.
- 你還是會吃的  - 是 也許我會的
- You're still gonna eat that. - Yeah, maybe I will.
這位打算去打業余賽了
This guy's actually fighting in an amateur night.
- 那可不是開玩笑的  - 關我屁事
- It's pretty badass. - I don't care.
我現在連零食都不能安安生生地吃了
Why can I not eat my snack,
毀掉我的露臺計劃 還要毀掉我的麥片酥嗎
or do you wanna ruin it, like my gazebo plan?
對一個喜歡看視頻的年輕性感的女士來說
There's no place safe for a young hot woman
在這里走路實在太不安全了
to just walk around, watching her internet videos.
年輕性感的女士 在哪里
Is there a young hot woman around?
哇哦 你慘了 你是在找打呢 動手
Whoa, those are fighting words. Fight him.
打他 打他 趁現在
Fight him right now. Fight him right now.
- 上吧 我們來格斗  - 哇 哇 哇
- Come on, let's fight. Let's wrestle. - Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- 哇 哇 哇  - 喂
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. - Man.
可憐的L醫生 她只是想要一個露臺而已
Poor Dr. L... All she was trying to do was make a gazebo
一個讓女孩可以和想象中的 或真實的朋友喝茶的地方
where a girl could have tea with her imaginary... real friends.
是啊 那些男人最過分了
Yeah, guys are the worst.
你知道今天是我和Ray Ron認識20周年的紀念日
Did you know today is me and Ray Ron's 20-year anniversary?
你覺得他會記得嗎
Do you think he remembered?
天哪 Ray Ron真遜啊
Ah, god, Ray Ron is a real scrub.
- 我能用這個詞嗎  - 可以
- Can I say that word? - Yeah.
- 那就好  - 他確實很遜
- Yes.  - He is a scrub.
今晚帶我出去吃飯會要他的命嗎
Would it have killed him to take me to a restaurant tonight
- 順便買輛新車  - 好吧
- ...and buy me a new car? - No.
我們是有過一輛車 可是他想不起來把它停哪兒了
We had a car, but Ray Ron can't remember where he parked it.
有時候我都不知道為什么還要和他繼續了
Sometimes I wonder why I'm with him.
既然你沒事 也許我們可以待晚一點
You know, since you're free, maybe we could kinda stay late
打掃打掃院子 給L醫生一個驚喜
and clean up the courtyard, surprise dr. L?
Morgan 這是個好主意
Morgan, that is a great idea.
我認為兩個人就夠了 我們在這兒待得晚一些
I think it's a two-person job, and we might be here kind of late.
你覺得呢 Tamra 要來嗎
What do you say, Tamra, should we do it?
反正我今晚也沒有浪漫晚餐什么的
It's not like I'm going on a romantic dinner or anything.
太好了
Yes!
我興奮是因為可以為L醫生做點事了 她人真的超棒
I'm just excited 'cause I think Dr. L is amazing.
還行吧
She's okay.
嘿
Hey.
- Peter為什么討厭我  - 你說什么呢
- How come Peter doesn't like me? - What are you talking about?
他總是暗地里損我 表現得很混蛋
He's always undermining me and being a jerk.
說實話 是因為我走路太大聲嗎
Be honest. Is it because I walk too loudly?
那是因為我鞋底很硬
My feet have very hard soles.
他不討厭你 他只是壓力太大了
He likes you. He's just stressed out.
哪來的壓力
Stressed out about what?
被發現他是Joran van der Sloot的朋友了
People finding out he's friends with Joran van der Sloot...
Joran van der Sloot美國一個少女失蹤案的主要犯罪嫌疑人
- 我這么覺得  - 好了 別亂想了
- I think. - Okay, take it easy.
他和女朋友分手了
He broke up with his girlfriend.
- Becca  - 是的
- Becca? - Yeah.
他們一年前就分了吧
They broke up, like, a year ago.
哦對了 我在facebook上關注了你所有前女友
Oh, I follow all of your exes on Facebook.
- 真的  - 嗯
- You do? - Yeah.
你為什么一定要每個人都喜歡你呢
Why do you have to get along with everyone you work with?
我們剛開始共事的時候關系也不好啊
We didn't get along when we first started working together.
對啊 我不喜歡那樣 現在不是好多了嗎
Yeah, and I hated that. Isn't it so much better now?
Peter就是不了解你而已
Look, Peter just doesn't know you.
我剛認識你的時候 我覺得你很煩
When I first met you, I thought you were annoying.
后來跟你熟了一點
And then I got to know you better,
我還是不喜歡你 但是現在我覺得你人很好
and I still didn't like you, and now I think you're a nice lady.
我們現在是朋友了 你應該和他吃頓飯
We're friends. Maybe you should take him to lunch.
- 你覺得那樣會好點兒嗎   - 當然
- Do you think that'll help? - Sure.
你嘴里塞滿了飯就沒那么多話了
With your mouth full, you can't talk that much.
- 好吧  - 什么 別鬧
- Okay. - What? Stop. Get...
我聽到了 給你個機會收回那句話
I heard you. I give you an opportunity to take it back.
- 好了 別鬧 你們好好玩兒   - 謝謝你的建議
- Alright. Stop, stop. Just have fun. - Thank you for the advice.
開心一點
Have fun.
我們來這兒干嘛
Hmm. Why are we here?
你已經在這兒上班了 我覺得我倆
Since you started working here, I feel like we haven't
好像一直沒機會好好了解對方
had a chance to really get to know each other.
然后你覺得帶我來美國女孩咖啡館
And you thought the best way to get to know me
就能了解我了
was to take me to the USA Girl Cafe?
你聽我說 很酷的
Actually, I have kind of a cool story.
我14歲第一次來例假的時候
When I first got my period at age 14,
我媽開車帶我們從馬賽諸塞州的康科德來到了這里
my mom drove us down from Concord, Massachusetts, to come here.
而且這家的嫩雞肉塊是城里最好的
Also, best chicken tenders in town.
- 我要走了  - 不不不 等下
- I'm gonna get out of here. - No. No, no, no, wait.
你對我有什么意見嘛
What is your problem with me?
我對你沒有意見啊
I don't have a problem with you.
我就是不想和你一起玩兒
I just don't wanna hang out with you if I don't have to.
可是為什么啊
But why don't you wanna hang out with me?
- 你有點兒自私  - 什么
- You're a little self-involved. - What?
如果你真想好好了解我
If you really wanted to get to know me at all,
你為什么不帶我去
why wouldn't you have taken
我倆都喜歡的地方呢
me to a place that we both could've enjoyed?
我都拿不住茶杯
I can't even hold the teacu...
這個把眼兒太小了 我的胖手指根本穿不過去
The holes on the teacups don't fit my fat fingers.
對不起 是我的失誤
I'm sorry. This was a miscalculation.
這個你肯定喜歡
But you know what you're gonna love?
我接下來要帶你去的地方
The place that I take you next...
皇冠香檳宮
Tiara's Champagne Palace.
Liberace的整形醫生就是在那逝世的
It is the death place of Liberace's plastic surgeon.
Liberace:美國著名的藝人和鋼琴家
這就是問題所在
You see, this is the thing.
你只愿意做那些你想做的事兒
You only wanna do things that you wanna do.
辦公室里其他人都跟著你一起
And all the other guys in the office
因為他們中間沒有像我這樣的人
would go along with it, because they didn't
給他們計劃一些有意思的事兒做
have a guy like me to make cool arrangements for them.
現在我來了 你就抓狂了
Now they do, and it's clearly driving you crazy.
真是不好意思了
So I'm sorry about that.
等下等下 我也可以和你們一起做那些事啊
Wait, wait, wait. I can do cool bro things too.
- 不行 拜拜  - 我沒有那么女孩子氣啦
- No, see ya. - I'm not as girly as you think.
Danny 你的建議真棒
Hey, great idea, Danny.
我帶Peter去了我最喜歡的飯館 簡直是一場災難
I took Peter to my favorite lunch place, and it was a disaster.
不是吧 你帶他去了那家
Oh, no. Did you take him to
娃娃館 還說了例假故事嗎
the doll place where you tell the period story?
是啊 他一點兒都不喜歡 你能相信嗎
Yeah, and he hated it. Can you believe that?
不能
No.
所以我要開始
So I would like to begin
寫正式的文件開除他了
the formal paperwork for his termination.
你得對Peter喜歡的東西
Look, you need to take an
有興趣才行
interest in something that Peter cares about.
再說最后一次 我才不要聽Phish的歌
For the last time, I will not listen to Phish.
歌曲就應該是時長三分鐘
Songs should be three minutes long,
中間有段Nicki Minaj的說唱
and Nicki Minaj raps in the middle.
我們今晚要去一家終極格斗館
Look, tonight we're going to this ultimate fighting thing.
- 你一起來吧  - 終極格斗
- You should come. - Ultimate fighting?
- 是的  - 不好意思 我寧愿去跟
- Yes. - I'm sorry. I'd rather do the mouse
困在我微波爐的老鼠格斗 也不要去那兒
that's trapped in my microwave than go to that.
你看 我說的就是這個
See, that's what I'm talking about.
你得努力嘗試一下 Peter會很感動的
You gotta make an effort. Peter will appreciate it.
我今晚要和Jason吃飯
I'm supposed to have dinner with Jason tonight.
- 就順路過來看看唄  - 好吧 我會去的
- Just stop by. - Okay, I'll go.
那就行
Good, go.
我給你帶了個友誼蛋糕
I got you a friendship cake.
謝謝你
Thank you.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
好了
Yes!
L醫生說的對
Man, Dr. L was right.
這上頭挺浪漫的
It's, uh, pretty romantic up here.
是啊 L醫生會高興瘋的
Yeah, dr. L's gonna freak out.
對了 沒有你我可做不來這些
Hey, I could not have done this without you, by the way.
其實做得來 說不定還會
I could've. It would've probably
更快點兒的 不過挺有意思的 所以
been a little quicker, but I had fun, so...
這可比Ray Ron計劃的每個紀念日都要好
This was better than any anniversary Ray Ron's ever planned.
去年我在機場就看著他上班
Last year, I just watched him work his shift at the airport.
你現在要不要和我一起出去吃點中餐
Do you wanna go with me right now and get Chinese food?
我知道一家飯館 他家份量可足了
'Cause I know this restaurant, they have such huge portions that
人們吃完了走出來
people walk out of the restaurant,
都會把他們的剩菜給你
they just give you their leftovers.
- 因為他們吃不完  - 所以他們以為你是流浪漢嗎
- They can't finish 'em. - So they think you're homeless?
不是 你有 哦
No, you get the l... Oh.
是啊 我還和Ray Ron在一起
Yeah. I'm still with Ray Ron.
- 改天吧  - 好的 好 好
- Maybe another time. - Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 以后再說  - 下次見
- We'll do it some other time. - All right, see you.
辦公室見 稍后見
I'll see you at the office, later on.
你在哪兒呢 我都吃了三碗毛豆了
Hey, where are you? I am already on my third bowl of edamame.
我會晚到30分鐘
I am going to be 30 minutes late...
45分鐘 最多一小時
45, an hour tops.
這種話應該白天提前說
Okay, that's something you tell me early in the day,
而不是在你已經遲到15分鐘的時候
not when you're already 15 minutes late.
我跟壽司師傅
The sushi chef and I are
真的已經沒話聊了
really running out of things to talk about.
- 那你們聊聊<絕命毒師>嘛  - 我就是從<絕命毒師>開始聊的
- Well, what about Breaking Bad? - I led with Breaking Bad.
我說Walter White是非英雄主角 他翻了個白眼
I said Walter White was an antihero, and he rolled his eyes.
Breaking Bad:剛完結的熱門美劇 Walter White為劇中主角
好吧 真是不好意思
Okay, I'm so sorry. But you know what?
不如你今晚過來吧
Why don't you come over tonight,
我保證我會做以前我不愿意做的那件事兒
and I promise I will do that thing that I told you I wouldn't do.
反正本來也打算做了
I was gonna do it anyway.
真的嗎
Really...?
有點意思
That's interesting.
既然你都到那兒了
Oh, and if you're at that place,
你可以嘗嘗費城壽司卷
you should get the Philadelphia roll.
Danny說特別棒 是他的最愛
Danny says it's amazing. It's his favorite.
知道了
Uh, duly noted.
我要掛了 Danny給我發短信了
Oh, I have to hang up. Danny's texting me.
你到哪兒了
該下車了
我怎么知道
我找對地兒了
噢 你看一眼
就知道了
*現在這玩意兒即將拉開序幕 這家伙看著古怪*
*It's about to kick off This party looks wack*
Eminem 新歌<Berzerk>
*讓我們回到直接的"嘻哈"*
*Let's take it back to*
*從頭開始*
*straight hip-hop And start it from scratch*
*我將要血洗這條賽道 所有人都閃開*
*I'm 'bout to bloody this track up, Everybody get back*
好了 好了
All right, all right.
- 擊倒他 擊倒他  - 噢
- Take him down, take him down! - Oh!
大伙兒 不好意思我來晚了
Hey, guys, sorry I was late.
我有點分心
I was distracted,
之前在和一個眼球穿洞的人說話
talking to a man who actually had a pierced eyeball.
- 噢  - 怎么了
- Ooh. - What's going on?
你來這兒干嘛
Why are you here?
MMA(Mixed Martial Arts),通常譯為綜合格斗或混合武術，
是一種規則極為開放的競技格斗運動
我們來支持Peter的 他在接受綜合格斗的訓練
We are here to support Peter. He's been training in MMA.
今晚是他的第一場比賽
Tonight is his first bout.
等下 你要到臺上去嗎
Wait. I'm sorry. You're going in there?
不不不 太危險了
No, no, no, no. That's not safe.
沒事兒 他會做地面捶擊
No way, man. He's gonna ground and pound.
Peter 你為什么要格斗
Peter, why would you do this?
這得追溯到小學 霸凌什么的
I guess it goes back to elementary school and all the bullying.
我知道了 你總是被別人欺負
Oh, I see. You were bullied, and martial arts
所以你學了格斗術保護自己
is the way that you stood up for yourself.
- 這就說得通了  - 什么 不是 是我欺負別人
- That makes sense. - What? No. I was the bully.
我的意思是如果那些小孩對綜合格斗感興趣
What I was saying was maybe if those kids were more into MMA,
也許我就會覺得他們很酷 就不欺負他們了
I would've thought they were cool and left them alone.
我覺得這個有點基啊
You know, it looks kind of homoerotic to me.
什么
What? There's nothing
和別人搏斗
homoerotic about grappling with another man,
把他打到地上 讓他屈服于你 哪里基了
pinning him to the ground, and making him succumb to your will.
我沒攻擊格斗 我喜歡格斗
No, I'm not dissing it. I like it.
這就對了 把他撕成兩半
That's right, tear him apart!
你倆真來電
You have great chemistry!
- 你在干嘛  - 什么 別這么說
- What are you doing? - What? No, don't do that.
你會讓我們死無葬身之地的
You're gonna get us killed.
這小妞真性感
This ring chick is so hot.
我的天
Oh, my God.
咱們怎么就不能辭了Beverly 雇這個姑娘呢
We can't fire Beverly and hire this girl, right?
伙計們 抱歉啊 他們只有啤酒
Hey, guys, I'm sorry, they only had beer.
我點了雞尾酒 但是他們沒有調酒的東西
I asked for mojitos, they didn't have the muddling equipment.
真是讓人震驚 在業余級MMA比賽
What a shock. They didn't
竟然沒有調酒的東西
have muddling equipment at an amateur MMA fight?
- 那才叫女人  - 真辣
- That's a woman. - Very hot.
我的天 我認識她
Oh, my God. I know her.
Marie 嗨
Marie, hi!
- Lahiri醫生  - 最近怎么樣
- Dr. Lahiri? - How's it going?
看見你真高興
So good to see you.
真不錯 Mindy有用了
This is good. Mindy's our in.
你的會陰切開術縫合恢復的怎么樣了
How are your episiotomy stitches healing?
你會用這種事起話頭嗎
Why would you start a conversation that way?
天呀 我的大女兒也剛生完
Oh, my God. My oldest just gave birth too.
我是姥姥了 你能相信么
I'm a grandmother. Can you believe it?
姥姥當家啊 恭喜恭喜
Granny in the house. Congratulations.
你知道衛生間在哪么
Do you know where the bathroom is?
等下 別別別 我幫你 我幫你
Oh, hold on. No, no, no. I got you, I got you.
你抬起后背
You gotta lift with your back.
準備好了嗎
Ready? One...
我的天
Oh, my God.
你里面裝的磚塊么
What, do you have bricks in here?
我的天啊 兄弟 抱歉抱歉
Oh, my God, dude. Sorry, sorry.
先生 先生 先生
Sir, sir, sir.
Morgan Tookers
Morgan Tookers.
我是你的鐵桿粉絲
I'm such a big fan of yours.
我經常看<換還是不換> 我自己在家也玩
I used to watch Deal or No Deal, and I would play along at home.
Deal or no deal 是美國一檔頗受歡迎的有獎競猜闖關智能型真人秀節目
- 愛死你的單口相聲了  - 我是UFC的Dana White
- I love your stand-up comedy. - I'm Dana White from the UFC.
UFC,即終極格斗冠軍賽,是目前世界上最頂級規模最龐大的職業MMA（綜合格斗）賽事
- 你不是Howie Mandel嗎  - 不是
- You're not Howie Mandel? - No.
Dana White 我比你的鐵桿粉絲還鐵桿
Dana White! Even bigger fan.
我給你發過我的錄像 在我家后院練MMA的
I send you videos of myself, of me doing some MMA in my backyard.
我希望成就一番格斗的榮耀
The glory in the quarry.
我完全聽不懂你說什么 也不知道你是誰
I have no idea what that is, and I don't know who you are.
但是我懂你 你這是裝酷
I know what you're doing. You're trying to play it cool,
那樣你就能低價簽下我
so you can, like, negotiate a cheaper contract for me.
在我這行不通 因為我免費簽給你
That's not gonna work, because I do it for free.
- 成吧 回頭聯系  - 你認真的么 你是
- All right. We'll be in touch. - Are you serious? Are you...
謝謝你 White先生
Thank you, Mr. White!
我馬上給自己起個藝名
We'll figure out my fighter name later.
打擾下 我有個消息要捎給Morgan Tooker
Excuse me. I got a message for Morgan Tookers.
內容是 有人要殺了你
It's in regards to straight-up killing him.
我能問下是誰么
May I ask who's calling?
- 我是Tamra的"小丑"男友Ray Ron  - 哦 是么
- I'm Tamra's clowned-on boyfriend Ray Ron.  - Oh, yeah.
好吧 一會見 冠軍
All right, see you later, champ.
- 你居然敢碰我  - 喔
- Don't you dare touch me! - Whoa!
- 這里禁止"常敗將軍"出沒  - 注意你的措辭
- This is a Jabroni-free zone. - Okay, watch your mouth.
Jabroni 是摔角比賽中的常用語 就是在比賽中經常輸的摔角手 跟小丑差不多
無通用譯法 這里譯為"常敗將軍" 歡迎指正
- 我爸爸就是個"常敗將軍" - 太瘋狂了
- My father was a Jabroni. - That's crazy, 'cause...
激怒我 讓我進入狀態
Get me angry, pump me up.
你個大胖子 大家都討厭你
You're a big fatty, and everybody hates you.
看出來你動腦子了 這個可以
Okay, it seems like you're projecting, but that's good.
嘿 要我說 你就是個一分不值的垃圾
Hey, you know what? You're a worthless piece of trash.
不錯啊 Mindy 這個不錯
Okay, that's good, Mindy, that's good.
昨晚我把你媽上了
Okay, I banged your mom last night.
- 哦 是么  - 是啊
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah!
- 昨晚我上了你爹  - 好吧
- I banged your dad last night. - Okay, okay.
- 我這個無敵好  - 是嗎
- Okay, I got a great one. - Yeah?
刷了下臉書 你前女友Becca剛訂婚了
According to Facebook, your ex-girlfriend Becca just got engaged!
是真的么
Is that real?
對 因為你一無是處 她早就把你拋在腦后
Yeah, 'cause you're such a loser, and she moved on.
憤怒起來吧
So get angry.
這是 是真的么 我能看一眼嗎
Is that... is that true? Can I see that?
- 是啊  - 那太
- Yeah. - That's...
啊 我是說我昨晚把你爸媽都上了 這個不錯
Uh, I mean, I banged your parents last night, so good.
他們很喜歡
Oh, they loved it.
她跟一個幼兒園男老師訂婚了
She got engaged to a male kindergarten teacher. From...
別管了 別念出來
Forget it. Don't read it.
他向她求婚的時候 整個班的學生都幫他
When he asked her to marry him, the class did it, and they...
- 他們拿著R的字母  - 很遺憾
- They're holding the "R" S backwards. - Sorry, man.
那家伙站在他的船邊看起來蠢爆了
That guy looks like a loser with his boat.
- 他看起來太高了 有一米九多呢  - 你做的夠糟了
- And he's, like, 6'4". - You're bad at this.
真棒啊 Mindy 真高興你做到了
That's great, Mindy. I'm really glad you made it.
才怪
Not.
穿藍色短褲的是新人Peter 懲罰者
In the blue trunks, Peter "The Punisher" Prentice.
Becca
Becca...
Becca 為什么
Becca, why?
沒關系的 沒事的
Okay, that's okay. You know what?
這是業余賽 他會沒事的
This is an amateur fight, so I think he'll be fine.
穿黑色短褲的Doug Lewis 被稱為 大屠殺
And in the black trunks, Doug "The Genocide" Lewis.
才不是 他已經害怕了
Yeah, no, he's terrifying.
喂 是911嗎 我想報告一起即將發生的死亡事件
Hello, 911, I'd like to report a death that hasn't happened yet.
不 不是我干的 但是我有責任
No, I didn't do it, but I am responsible.
哦不 哦天啊
Oh, no. Oh, God.
- 哦 Pete  - 哦 天啊 Peter
- Oh, Pete. - Oh, God, Peter.
我來這兒就是個錯誤
I made a mistake, doing this.
不要啊 Peter Peter Peter
No, Peter, Peter, Peter!
- 哦  - 天啊 怎么了
- Oh! - God. What is happening?
Peter就站在那兒挨打
Peter is just standing there and taking it,
就像鄉村音樂電影里的小媳婦一樣
like he's the wife in a country music movie.
你跟Peter共事了這么久
How could you work with Peter all these months
怎么還不知道不能在他面前提Becca呢
and not know that mentioning Becca would destroy him?
- 都快成明文規定了 Lahiri  - 行了
- It's textbook Lahiri. - Okay.
還是注意下咱們的朋友吧
Let's focus on our friend.
我們必須把他弄出去
Okay, you know what, we have got to get him out of there.
- Pete 裝死吧  - 我不敢看了 哦
- Pete, just play dead! - I cannot watch. Oh...
- 哦不 Pete 不 Pete  - 別打了
- Oh, no, Pete. No, Pete. - Get beaten up less.
- 誰都不能覬覦我女朋友  - 我可不想打架 哥們
- Nobody scams on my girlfriend! - I don't wanna fight, dude.
我就是來給你這個
I just came to give you this.
- 什么  - 哦
- What? - Ohh!
Peter Peter 哦 不
Peter, Peter. Oh, no.
Marie Marie Marie
Marie, Marie, Marie.
麻煩你了 我得進里面去
Please, I need to get in the ring.
抱歉 能進去的人只有
I'm sorry, the only people allowed in the ring
想死的或者露胸的
are people willing to die or flash their boobs.
如果你幫我這個忙 下次你生孩子
If you do me this favor, the next time you give birth,
我保證給你總統套房
I promise you I will get you the celebrity suite.
我才不管是要踢走Ice-T還是Coco
I don't care if I have to kick out Ice-T and Coco.
現在才發現她們的名字都是飲料
I'm only now realizing that both of their names are drinks.
啊
Aa!
哦天啊 你覺得呢
Oh, God. What do you say?
- 馬上是第二輪  - 把你上衣脫了
- It's time for round two! - Take your top off!
不好意思 先生
Excuse me, sir, I'm just here
我僅僅是過來告訴你們接下來是第幾輪的
to convey numerical information about which round it is.
哦天啊 Mindy
Oh, God, Mindy.
- 嘿 看我  - 你干什么呢
- Hey, look at me! - What are you doing?
行了 下來 你會受傷的
All right, get down. You're gonna get hurt.
我覺得人們會喜歡的 哦不 他們沒反應
I think people like it. No, they're not responding to it.
有反應了 他們不喜歡 不喜歡
They hate it. They hate it, okay.
現在我們診所一半的醫生都在臺上了
That is 50% of the surgeons in our practice.
嘿 嘿 嘿 聽我說
Hey, hey, hey, listen to me.
- 你必須退出  - 我不能退出 懦夫才那樣做
- You need to quit. - I can't quit. I'll look like a wuss.
那也比死了或者癱瘓強啊
That is better than being dead or paralyzed.
不 不會的
No, it's not.
對于一個男人沒什么比退出更糟了
Not for a dude it's not.
我是說 退出確實是好辦法 但不是男人的選擇
I mean, it is, it's way better, but not for a dude.
嘿 嘿 Peter 那家伙就跟地獄之門的看守似的
Hey, hey, Peter. That guy looks like he guards the gates to hell.
- 他會殺了你的  - 他應該把我殺了
- He's going to kill you. - He should.
他應該帶我離開我的這些不幸
He should put me out of my misery.
嘿 嘿 嘿 別說傻話
Hey, hey, hey, this is dumb.
嘿 嘿 活起來 活起來
Hey, hey, look alive, look alive.
為什么今天所有人都要打我的臉啊
Why is everyone hitting me in the face today?
因為你需要被打醒
Because you need to get smacked, son.
你要么就退出比賽下去
You either need to get out of this ring and quit,
要么就盡全力以赴
or you need to really buckle down.
全力以赴 你以為我在寫家庭作業么
Buckle down? What, am I doing homework?
如果你必須打 那你得
If you're gonna do this, you need to picture
把那個家伙想象成你討厭的人
that the other guy is someone that you hate.
我堅持上動感單車課唯一的方法就是假裝
The only way that I get through spin class is that I pretend
自己不停碾壓Michael Jackson的醫生的身體
that I'm running over the body of that Michael Jackson doctor...
那個把Michael Jackson奪走的人
The one that stole Michael Jackson from us.
我恨死他了
I hate that guy!
我恨你 Michael Jackson的醫生 奪走了Michael
I hate you, Michael Jackson doctor, for taking away Michael!
你就那么想象 好嗎 Peter Peter 看著我
Just do that with him. Okay, Peter? Peter, look at me.
Peter 我相信你 你能做到的
Peter, I believe in you. You can do this.
- 我確實恨一個人  - 很好
- Here's someone I hate. - Yes!
- 我恨Becca的未婚夫  - 很好 保持恨意
- I hate Becca's fiance. - Great, that's perfect.
- 他是個幼兒園老師  - 沒錯
- He's a kindergarten teacher. - Yes.
誰會去幼兒園當老師啊
Who teaches kindergarten?
還是在市中心的幼兒園
And he does it in the inner city, no less.
- 這倒不錯  - 上吧
- That's nice. - Let's go, beard-o!
很好 很好
Okay, good.
- 夠了嗎  - 垃圾就應該進垃圾桶里
- Had enough? - Yeah, I put my trash the trash.
別 別哭 拜托 不要
Don't... don't cry, please. Don't...
過來吧 快 出來吧
Come on, man. Come on, get out of there.
好的 天哪 出來吧
Yeah. Oh, God. Get out of there.
我 我只是不想失去Tamra
I-I just don't wanna lose Tamra.
她是我生命中最美好的事情 我可是有一張水床的
She's the best thing I got. And I own a water bed, man.
哼 被甩也是你自找的 昨天你去哪了
Yeah, well, maybe you deserve to lose her. What was yesterday?
- 是你們的紀念日啊  - 哦 要死
- It was your anniversary. - Oh, damn.
我以為是上個月 我以為已經過去了
I thought it was last month, and I was in the clear.
顯然 沒有
Yeah, well, it's not.
好吧
Okay, look.
我做這些都是因為Tamra在乎你
I'm only doing this because Tamra cares about you.
但是一旦有了女朋友 兄弟 你就得一切以她為中心
But when you have a girlfriend, man, you gotta be all about her.
24小時在她身邊
You gotta be up in her grill 24/7.
用愛緊緊地捆綁住她
You have to smother them with love.
不過 這可能也是我一直戀愛失敗的原因
I mean, that's why none of mine work out.
我也不知道了
I don't know.
- 也許這是個爛建議  - 不 這很好
- Maybe that's bad advice. - No, that's good advice.
- 我確實要采取行動了  - 對啊
- I need to do something big. - Yeah...
這件事必須要有送珠寶的效果
Like, something that has
但是又不花一分錢
the effect of jewelry, but costs no money.
好吧 聽著不錯
Yeah, that sounds great.
謝謝你 Morgan
Thank you, Morgan.
來吧
Come on.
不過再有第二次 我就要偷走你的女朋友了
That happens again, though, I'm gonna steal your girlfriend.
- 我是認真的  - 什么
- I'm serious. - What...?
很好 Peter 很好
That's good, Peter, that's good.
保持一定距離
Just keep away from him.
- 上啊  - 加油 Peter
- Go, Pete! - Come on, Peter!
噢
Oh! Ugh.
- 啊  - Pete
- Ahh! - Pete!
干的好 Peter
Yes, Peter!
哇 看來你的打氣確實起作用了
Wow. It looks like your pep talk did him some good.
所以我說嘛 我應該去當
This is why I think I should
高收入的勵志演說家
be one of those highly paid motivational speakers.
嘿 我錯過了什么
Ah, hey, what'd I miss?
啊
Aah!
天哪
Oh, God!
好了
Okay...
那些人沒看到我哭吧
You don't think the crowd saw me crying, do you?
絕對沒有
No, they definitely didn't.
因為大部分時間
Because most of the time,
你的臉都在另外那個家伙的襠部
your face was smushed into that guy's crotch.
- 謝天謝地  - 是啊
- Oh, thank God... - Yeah.
那個女孩真的傷到你了 是吧
That girl really did a number on you, huh?
只是對她的未婚夫感到同情罷了
Mostly I feel bad for her new fiance,
他馬上就要去應對她的破事兒了
he's gonna have to deal with all her issues, you know.
所有最高法院的法官
All those Supreme Court
都不停地往他們家打電話 從不消停
justices calling the house all the time...
"做我的助理吧 做我的助理吧"
"Clerk for me, clerk for me..."
我知道這并不是啥光榮的事 但是
I know it's not the brilliest of things, but...
說到吐槽前任 可是我的競技專業
If you ever wanna gossip your ex-es, that's like my MMA.
- 這個運動術語用對了嗎  - 沒有
- Is that a good sport technology. - No...
- 好吧  - 不過謝謝你
- OK. - But thank you.
我感覺有點喜歡你了
I might take you up on that.
我從Danny的各種戀情里學到的就是
The most I get about relationships from Danny is like...
"沒什么特別 但就是那么回事兒"
"Nothing, but it is what it is."
很抱歉 我之前錯了
I'm sorry, I was wrong.
別擔心 你會沒事的
Don't worry about it. You're gonna be OK.
而且說真的
And, to be honest, when you're
沒和那群家伙在一起的時候 你還不賴
not around the other guys, you're not that bad.
謝謝 我止痛藥吃嗨了
Thanks. When I'm high on painkillers,
感覺你的聲音也沒那么尖銳了
your voice isn't that shrill.
好吧 謝謝 這樣非常好 Peter
Oh, a'right. Thanks, that's very nice of you, Peter.
你是真嗨了 對吧
You are pretty high right now, aren't you?
嘿
Hey...
- 嘿  - 真是大驚喜
- Hi. - What a nice surprise...
天哪 天哪 我忘記了
Oh my God, oh my God... I
今晚我們本來要在我家約會的
was supposed to meet you back at my apartment.
- 聽著 Mindy 我覺得你很好  - 你也很好
- Look, Mindy, I think you're great. - And I think you are great.
對話就此結束
And that could just be the end of the conversation,
你不需要繼續了
you don't need to continue in it.
不 Mindy 我覺得你很好 但是
No. Mindy, I think you're great. But...
- 對不起我忘了我們的計劃  - 兩次
- I am so sorry I forgot about our plans. - Twice.
只是 我覺得工作很重要
It's just... I felt that it was important that I go for work.
你就沒有因為工作而被迫去做一些事嗎
Haven't you ever had to do something because of work?
當然有啊
Yeah! Sure. I just went
我剛剛去參加我老板小孩的中學畢業典禮
to my boss's kids middle school graduation.
但那并不意味我能記得她最愛的壽司
But that doesn't mean I memorized her favorite sushi order.
抱歉 Mindy
I'm sorry, Mindy.
我要...
I'm gonna...
再見
Goodbye.
嗨 我想見你們這最性感的護士
Hello. I'd like to speak to your sexiest nurse.
哦 Mogan
Mogan!
Ray Ron 你來做什么
Ray Ron, what do you want?
Tamra 我是世界上最傻的人
Tamra, I'm the dumbest guy on earth.
我是說 一整個紀念日
I mean, to think I spent our entire anniversary
我都在垃圾堆里 想翻點貨出來
trying to find stuff in the garage, then my work is drugs.
- 沒錯 你是個白癡  - 嗯 但是我會彌補的
- Yeah, you're an idiot. - Yeah, but I'm about to make it up.
我剛剛用圖書館的電腦查了
'Cause I used a library computer just to find out
20年紀念日的最佳禮物
that the right gift for our twentieth anniversary
是中國
is China.
你為我去用電腦了
You used a computer for me?
雖然我不能送你整個國家
And while I can't afford the whole country...
- 但我有這個  - 噢
- I got you this. - Aw...
我要叫你Nuka 因為那是我真正想要的
Imma call you Nuka, 'cause that's what I really wanted...
小妞 我要帶你去一家有菜單的餐廳
Girl... Imma take you to a menu restaurant.
Morgan 你能幫我代班嗎
Morgan. Can you cover for me?
好吧 當然 我愿意為你做任何事 Tamra
Yes! Yes, sure, I'll do anything... For you, Tamra.
這次你去給小費 RayRon
And this time you're tippin' the waiter, Ray Ron...
等等 什么
Wait, wha...
- 真是一對好情侶啊  - 你才是好情侶
- They are a great couple. - You're a great couple!
噢 謝謝
Oh, thank you.
先生們 睜開眼睛
Gentlemen, open your eyes.
很高興向你們介紹
I would like to introduce
Peter的"懲罰者"
to you the Peter "The Punisher" Prentice
- 紀念籃球公園  - 我搭好的露臺呢
- ...Memorial Basketball Park. - What happened to the gazebo?
它在我心中
There is a gazebo in my heart.
Mindy 這實在是
Mindy, this is...
- 不可思議  - 太令人驚訝
- Unbelievable. - So amazing...
- 你來投第一個球吧  - 真的嗎
- Take the first shot. - Really?
- 當然  - 好吧 酷
- Yeah, of course! - OK. Cool!
- 謝謝你 Peter  - 我謝謝你才對 這太棒了
- Thank you, Peter. - Thank you, this is awesome.
- 噢 噢 兄弟  - 拜托
- Oh, oh, dude... - Come on...
- 搞什么啊  - 這才是和哥們打球的方式
- What the hell? - That's how bros play...
好吧
All right.
- 謝謝你  - 打得好
- Thank you. - Good shot.
- 喂 Peter  - 不是吧
- Peter, dude... - Come on, Peter!
- 你玩我呢  - 行動判斷失誤
- You gotta be kidding me. - Misread the moment.
- 太遺憾了  - 對我還是對籃球公園
- So sorry. - For me or the basketball park?
就是遺憾
So sorry!
電波字幕組 歡迎您的加入
官方網站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@電波字幕組